Guide to the Stanford University, Class of 1979, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Class of 1979, records
1975-1989
SC0779
Sanchez, Andrew, collector
1 Linear feet amd 132 megabytes
Collection pertains to student life at Stanford and includes programs, booklets, publications, clippings, flyers, newsletters, photographs, and other items. Of note are items pertaining to the Mexican American community and Casa Zapata.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Collection pertains to student life at Stanford and includes programs, booklets, publications, clippings, flyers, newsletters, photographs, and other items. Of note are items pertaining to the Mexican American community and Casa Zapata.
Access Terms
Sanchez, Andrew, collector; Stanford University. Class of 1979.; Mexican American students --California --Stanford.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Latino/Chicano Life (includes Casa Zapata items and material for Chicano community meeting March 1977), 1977-79 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1977-81 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Events Around Campus, 1975-79 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 30 computer file(s) (TIFF) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Musicals and music at Stanford, including dorm events, 1975-79 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academics – human biology and psychology, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Commencement and Reunions, 1979, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Living at Stanford (course lists, Stanford Bulletins, residence halls) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Directory – Mirlo dorm room lists (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Directories, 1975-76 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Directories, 1977-79 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stanford book cover (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Kazoo (Box 2, Folder 5)